A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Political Files, Series 24 FA367
Rockefeller Archive Center
- 1961-1962, 2; 12 Cubic Feet
  - New York State Republican Matters - Nixon-Rockefeller Agreement (Box 20, Folder 778)
  - New York State Republican Matters - 1960 Election Figures for Members of New York State Assembly (Box 20, Folder 779)
  - New York State Republican Matters - New York City Republican Program (Box 20, Folder 780)
  - New York State Republican Matters - Republican Form Letters (Box 20, Folder 781)
  - New York State Republican Matters - 1960 Election Congratulatory Telegrams (Box 20, Folder 782)
  - New York State Republican Matters - Monthly Speech Index (Box 20, Folder 783)
  - New York State Republican Matters - New York State Republican Yearbook (Box 20, Folder 784)
  - New York State Republican Matters - Citizens for Rockefeller and Javits (Box 20, Folder 785)
  - New York State Republican Matters - Conservative Party Material (Box 20, Folder 786)
  - New York State Republican Matters - Acceptance Speeches (Box 20, Folder 787)
  - New York State Republican Matters - 1962 New York State Campaign Material (Box 20, Folder 788)
  - New York State Republican Matters - 1962 Campaign Issues (Box 20, Folder 789)
  - Out-of-State Republican Matters - 1960 Republican Platform (Box 20, Folder 790)
  - Out-of-State Republican Matters - United Republican Finance Committee (Box 20, Folder 791)
  - Out-of-State Republican Matters - Fund Raising Material (Box 20, Folder 792)
  - Out-of-State Republican Matters - Republican National Committee (Box 20, Folder 793)
  - Out-of-State Republican Matters - Republican National Committee Itineraries (Box 20, Folder 794)
  - Out-of-State Republican Matters - Republican Committee on Program and Progress (Box 20, Folder 795)
  - Out-of-State Republican Matters - Delegates to 1960 National Convention (Box 20, Folder 796)
  - Out-of-State Republican Matters - Figures on 1960 Election (Box 20, Folder 797)
  - Miscellaneous Materials (Box 20, Folder 798)
  - Speech Outlines (Box 20, Folder 799)
  - Basic Factual Material (Box 20, Folder 800)
  - Quotes and Background Memos (Box 20, Folder 801)
  - Letter to the GOP Community Chairmen (Box 20, Folder 802)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (A), 1961 (Box 20, Folder 803)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (B), 1961 (Box 20, Folder 804)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (C), 1961 (Box 20, Folder 805)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (D), 1961 (Box 20, Folder 806)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (E), 1961 (Box 20, Folder 807)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (F), 1961 (Box 20, Folder 808)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (G), 1961 (Box 20, Folder 809)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (H), 1961 (Box 20, Folder 810)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (I), 1961 (Box 20, Folder 811)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (J), 1961 (Box 20, Folder 812)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (K), 1961 (Box 20, Folder 813)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (L), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 814)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (M), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 815)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (N), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 816)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (O), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 817)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (P), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 818)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (R), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 819)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (S), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 820)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (T), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 821)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (U), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 822)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (V), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 823)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (W), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 824)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Y), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 825)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (A), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 826)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ai), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 827)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Am), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 828)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (As), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 829)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (B), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 830)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Be), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 831)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Bi), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 832)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Bo), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 833)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Bu), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 834)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (C), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 835)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ce), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 836)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ci), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 837)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Co), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 838)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Cu), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 839)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (D), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 840)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (De), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 841)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Di), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 842)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Do), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 843)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Du), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 844)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (E), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 845)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ei), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 846)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Em), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 847)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ev), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 848)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (F), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 849)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Fe), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 850)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Fu), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 851)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (G), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 852)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ge), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 853)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Gi), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 854)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Go), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 855)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (H), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 856)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (He), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 857)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hi), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 858)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ho), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 859)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hu), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 860)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (I), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 861)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (J), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 862)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Jo), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 863)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ju), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 864)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (K), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 865)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ke), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 866)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ki), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 867)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ko), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 868)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (L), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 869)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Le), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 870)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Li), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 871)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (M), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 872)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mc), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 873)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Me), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 874)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mi), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 875)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mo), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 876)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mu), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 877)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (N), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 878)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ne), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 879)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ni), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 880)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (O), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 881)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (P), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 882)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pe), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 883)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pi), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 884)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Q), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 885)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (R), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 886)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Re), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 887)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ri), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 888)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ro), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 889)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ru), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 890)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (S), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 891)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sch), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 892)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Se), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 893)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Si), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 894)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (So), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 895)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Su), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 896)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (T), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 897)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ti), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 898)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (U), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 899)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (V), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 900)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (W), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 901)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Y), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 902)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Z), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 903)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Hi), 1961 (Box 23, Folder 904)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Ho), 1961 (Box 23, Folder 905)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (I), 1961 (Box 23, Folder 906)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (J), 1961 (Box 23, Folder 907)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (K), 1961 (Box 23, Folder 908)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (L), 1961 (Box 23, Folder 909)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (M), 1961 (Box 23, Folder 910)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (P), 1961 (Box 23, Folder 911)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (R), 1961 (Box 23, Folder 912)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (S), 1961 (Box 23, Folder 913)
  - New york State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (T), 1961 (Box 23, Folder 914)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (U), 1961 (Box 23, Folder 915)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (V), 1961 (Box 23, Folder 916)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (W), 1961 (Box 23, Folder 917)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Y), 1961 (Box 23, Folder 918)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (A), 1962 (Box 23, Folder 919)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Am), 1962 (Box 23, Folder 920)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (B), 1962 (Box 23, Folder 921)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Be), 1962 (Box 23, Folder 922)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Bi), 1962 (Box 23, Folder 923)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Bo), 1962 (Box 23, Folder 924)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Bu), 1962 (Box 23, Folder 925)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (C), 1962 (Box 23, Folder 926)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ce), 1962 (Box 23, Folder 927)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ci), 1962 (Box 23, Folder 928)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Co), 1962; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 23, Folder 929)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Co), 1962; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 23, Folder 930)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Cu), 1962 (Box 23, Folder 931)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (D), 1962 (Box 24, Folder 932)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (De), 1962 (Box 24, Folder 933)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Du), 1962 (Box 24, Folder 934)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (E), 1962 (Box 24, Folder 935)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (F), 1962 (Box 24, Folder 936)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (G), 1962; Folder 1 of 3 (Box 24, Folder 937)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (G), 1962; Folder 2 of 3 (Box 24, Folder 938)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (G), 1962; Folder 3 of 3 (Box 24, Folder 939)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (H), 1962 (Box 24, Folder 940)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (He), 1962 (Box 24, Folder 941)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ho), 1962 (Box 24, Folder 942)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (I), 1962 (Box 24, Folder 943)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (J), 1962 (Box 24, Folder 944)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (K), 1962 (Box 25, Folder 945)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (L), 1962 (Box 25, Folder 946)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Li), 1962 (Box 25, Folder 947)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Lu), 1962 (Box 25, Folder 948)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (M), 1962; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 25, Folder 949)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (M), 1962; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 25, Folder 950)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mc), 1962 (Box 25, Folder 951)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mi), 1962 (Box 25, Folder 952)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mo), 1962 (Box 25, Folder 953)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mu), 1962 (Box 25, Folder 954)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (N), 1962 (Box 25, Folder 955)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (O), 1962 (Box 25, Folder 956)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (P), 1962 (Box 25, Folder 957)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Q), 1962 (Box 25, Folder 958)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (R), 1962; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 26, Folder 959)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (R), 1962; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 26, Folder 960)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (S), 1962 (Box 26, Folder 961)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Se), 1962 (Box 26, Folder 962)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (So), 1962 (Box 26, Folder 963)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Su), 1962 (Box 26, Folder 964)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (T), 1962 (Box 26, Folder 965)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (U), 1962 (Box 26, Folder 966)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (V), 1962 (Box 26, Folder 967)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (W), 1962; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 26, Folder 968)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (W), 1962; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 26, Folder 969)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Y), 1962 (Box 26, Folder 970)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Z), 1962 (Box 26, Folder 971)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (A), 1962 (Box 26, Folder 972)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (B), 1962 (Box 26, Folder 973)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Co), 1962 (Box 26, Folder 974)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (D), 1962 (Box 27, Folder 975)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (E), 1962 (Box 27, Folder 976)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (F), 1962 (Box 27, Folder 977)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (G), 1962 (Box 27, Folder 978)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (H), 1962 (Box 27, Folder 979)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (J), 1962 (Box 27, Folder 980)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (K), 1962 (Box 27, Folder 981)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (L), 1962 (Box 27, Folder 982)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (M), 1962; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 27, Folder 983)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (M), 1962; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 27, Folder 984)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (N), 1962 (Box 27, Folder 985)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (O), 1962 (Box 27, Folder 986)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (P), 1962 (Box 27, Folder 987)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Q), 1962 (Box 27, Folder 988)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (R), 1962 (Box 27, Folder 989)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (S), 1962 (Box 27, Folder 990)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (T), 1962 (Box 27, Folder 991)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (U), 1962 (Box 27, Folder 992)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (V), 1962 (Box 27, Folder 993)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (W), 1962 (Box 27, Folder 994)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Y), 1962 (Box 27, Folder 995)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Z), 1962 (Box 27, Folder 996)
  - County Briefing Notes - Albany County, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 997)
  - County Briefing Notes - Allegany County, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 998)
  - County Briefing Notes - Broome County, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 999)
  - County Briefing Notes - Cattaraugus County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1000)
  - County Briefing Notes - Cayuga County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1001)
  - County Briefing Notes - Chautauqua County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1002)
  - County Briefing Notes - Chemung County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1003)
  - County Briefing Notes - Chenango County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1004)
  - County Briefing Notes - Clinton County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1005)
  - County Briefing Notes - Columbia County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1006)
  - County Briefing Notes - Delaware County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1007)
  - County Briefing Notes - Dutchess County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1008)
  - County Briefing Notes - Erie County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1009)
  - County Briefing Notes - Essex County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1010)
  - County Briefing Notes - Franklin County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1011)
  - County Briefing Notes - Fulton County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1012)
  - County Briefing Notes - Genesee County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1013)
  - County Briefing Notes - Greene County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1014)
  - County Briefing Notes - Hamilton County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1015)
  - County Briefing Notes - Herkimer County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1016)
  - County Briefing Notes - Jefferson County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1017)
  - County Briefing Notes - Lewis County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1018)
  - County Briefing Notes - Madison County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1019)
  - County Briefing Notes - Monroe County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1020)
  - County Briefing Notes - Montgomery County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1021)
  - County Briefing Notes - Nassau County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1022)
  - County Briefing Notes - Niagara County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1023)
  - County Briefing Notes - Oneida County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1024)
  - County Briefing Notes - Onondaga County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1025)
  - County Briefing Notes - Orange County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1026)
  - County Briefing Notes - Orleans County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1027)
  - County Briefing Notes - Otsego County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1028)
  - County Briefing Notes - Putnam County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1029)
  - County Briefing Notes - Rensselaer County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1030)
  - County Briefing Notes - Richmond County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1031)
  - County Briefing Notes - Rockland County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1032)
  - County Briefing Notes - St. Lawrence County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1033)
  - County Briefing Notes - Saratoga County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1034)
  - County Briefing Notes - Schenectady County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1035)
  - County Briefing Notes - Schoharie County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1036)
  - County Briefing Notes - Seneca County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1037)
  - County Briefing Notes - Steuben County, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1038)
  - County Briefing Notes - Suffolk County, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 1039)
  - County Briefing Notes - Sullivan County, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 1040)
  - County Briefing Notes - Tioga County, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 1041)
  - County Briefing Notes - Tompkins County, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 1042)
  - County Briefing Notes - Ulster County, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 1043)
  - County Briefing Notes - Warren County, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 1044)
  - County Briefing Notes - Washington County, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 1045)
  - County Briefing Notes - Westchester County, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 1046)
  - County Briefing Notes - Wyoming County, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 1047)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Anonymous, 1961; Folder 1 of 24 (Box 29, Folder 1048)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Anonymous, 1961; Folder 2 of 24 (Box 29, Folder 1049)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Anonymous, 1961; Folder 3 of 24 (Box 29, Folder 1050)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Anonymous, 1961; Folder 4 of 24 (Box 29, Folder 1051)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Anonymous, 1961; Folder 5 of 24 (Box 29, Folder 1052)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Anonymous, 1961; Folder 6 of 24 (Box 29, Folder 1053)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Anonymous, 1961; Folder 7 of 24 (Box 29, Folder 1054)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Anonymous, 1961; Folder 8 of 24 (Box 29, Folder 1055)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Anonymous, 1961; Folder 9 of 24 (Box 30, Folder 1056)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Anonymous, 1961; Folder 10 of 24 (Box 30, Folder 1057)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Anonymous, 1961; Folder 11 of 24 (Box 30, Folder 1058)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Anonymous, 1961; Folder 12 of 24 (Box 30, Folder 1059)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Anonymous, 1961; Folder 13 of 24 (Box 30, Folder 1060)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Anonymous, 1961; Folder 14 of 24 (Box 30, Folder 1061)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Anonymous, 1961; Folder 15 of 24 (Box 30, Folder 1062)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Anonymous, 1961; Folder 16 of 24 (Box 30, Folder 1063)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Anonymous, 1961; Folder 17 of 24 (Box 30, Folder 1064)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Anonymous, 1961; Folder 18 of 24 (Box 30, Folder 1065)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Anonymous, 1961; Folder 19 of 24 (Box 30, Folder 1066)